timex.com 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy | Casual, Dress, and Sport Watches for Women & Men

**Privacy Statement**

Timex.com, Inc. believes that you, as our online visitor, have the right to know our practices regarding any information we might collect when you visit our website.

For each visitor to the Timex.com website, our web server automatically recognizes and stores information, such as the visitor IP address and domain name. We track such information to perform internal research on our users' demographic interests and behavior and to better understand, protect and serve our customers and community. We also use data collection devices such as "cookies." Cookies are small files placed on a visitor's hard drive that assist us in providing products and services to our customers. You are always free to decline "cookies if your browser permits. In addition, a visitor may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

In addition, we may ask you to provide personal information on our website shopping cart when you choose to buy a product or service. This information may include your name, mailing address, phone number, credit card number, all of which are necessary to the ordering of products/services on Timex.com. Timex.com, Inc., its parent, subsidiary and other affiliated companies may use this information to improve their marketing and promotional efforts as well as to improve the user experience on the Timex.com website. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your express consent. However, your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business of providing goods and services to customers, including but not limited to, advertisers, third party service providers and law enforcement authorities.

Timex.com may contact you to provide information about products, services, promotions, contests or other offerings. We do this only on an opt-in basis. That is, you have the option of checking or removing the check from the box indicating your preference on receiving future Timex.com communications.

In the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your personal information and private communications will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the website. Timex.com takes measures to safeguard your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access to that information in its internal procedures and technology. However, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information and private communications will always remain private.

Other websites that may be linked to/from the Timex.com website may have different policies. You should review the policies on these other websites to understand their policies and practices.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Timex.com website. All amended terms shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted on the website.

**Secure Ordering**

Protecting your order information is our first concern. Timex.com makes every effort to protect your online order information by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, with a digital certificate provided by VeriSign.

Effective Date: April 27, 2015
